{
  "questions":[
  {
      "qid": "p1u1-e1",
      "questionType": "fillInBlank",
      "question": "Miss Chan is my favourite _________. She teaches me English.",
      "answers": ["principal", "student", "teacher"],
      "correctAnswer": "teacher"
  },
  {
      "qid": "p1u1-e2",
      "questionType": "fillInBlank",
      "question": "It’s time to go, let’s say __________ to Aunt Lily.",
      "answers": ["good morning", "good night", "goodbye"],
      "correctAnswer": "goodbye"
  },
  {
      "qid": "p1u1-e3",
      "questionType": "fillInBlank",
      "question": "Mr Lee made Tom a ________and he is happy about it.",
      "answers": ["monitor", "monita", "monika"],
      "correctAnswer": "monitor"
  },
  {
      "qid": "p1u1-e4",
      "questionType": "fillInBlank",
      "question": "Leo and I are____________. We are in the same class.",
      "answers": ["students", "classmates", "teachers"],
      "correctAnswer": "classmates"
  },
  {
      "qid": "p1u1-e5",
      "questionType": "fillInBlank",
      "question": "Amy is my best _______ and we always share secrets to each other.",
      "answers": ["friend", "teacher", "student"],
      "correctAnswer": "friend"
  },
  {
      "qid": "p1u1-e6",
      "questionType": "fillInBlank",
      "question": "You can ask a ________to help you find books.",
      "answers": ["library", "prefect", "librarian"],
      "correctAnswer": "librarian"
  },
  {
      "qid": "p1u1-e7",
      "questionType": "fillInBlank",
      "question": "We should ____ others when we see them.",
      "answers": ["greek", "greed", "greet"],
      "correctAnswer": "greet"
  },
  {
      "qid": "p1u1-e8",
      "questionType": "fillInBlank",
      "question": "Who is the group ______?",
      "answers": ["cleaner", "leader", "lender"],
      "correctAnswer": "leader"
  },
  {
      "qid": "p1u1-e9",
      "questionType": "fillInBlank",
      "question": "He says good __________ to us first thing every day.",
      "answers": ["morning", "evening", "afternoon"],
      "correctAnswer": "morning"
  },
  {
      "qid": "p1u1-e10",
      "questionType": "fillInBlank",
      "question": "Sorry, do you know where the ________’s office is?",
      "answers": ["principal", "principle", "princess"],
      "correctAnswer": "principal"
  },
  {
    "qid": "p1u2-a1",
    "questionType": "audio",
    "question": "femily, families, family",
    "answers": ["femily", "families", "family"],
    "correctAnswer": "family"
  },
  {
      "qid": "p1u2-a2",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "mother, father, sister",
      "answers": ["mother", "father", "sister"],
      "correctAnswer": "sister"
  },
  {
      "qid": "p1u2-a3",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "mother, father, sister",
      "answers": ["mother", "father", "sister"],
      "correctAnswer": "father"
  },
  {
      "qid": "p1u2-a4",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "mother, sister, brother",
      "answers": ["mother", "sister", "brother"],
      "correctAnswer": "mother"
  },
  {
      "qid": "p1u2-a5",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "mother, sister, brother",
      "answers": ["mother", "sister", "brother"],
      "correctAnswer": "brother"
  },
  {
      "qid": "p1u2-a6",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "grandma, grandmother, grandfather",
      "answers": ["grandma", "grandmother", "grandfather"],
      "correctAnswer": "grandmother"
  },
  {
      "qid": "p1u2-a7",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "grandmother, grandpa, grandfather",
      "answers": ["grandmother", "grandpa", "grandfather"],
      "correctAnswer": "grandfather"
  },
  {
      "qid": "p1u2-a8",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "parrots, parants, parents",
      "answers": ["parrots", "parants", "parents"],
      "correctAnswer": "parents"
  },
  {
      "qid": "p1u2-a9",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "children, chilldren, childrens",
      "answers": ["children", "chilldren", "childrens"],
      "correctAnswer": "children"
  },
  {
      "qid": "p1u2-a10",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "babies, baby, babe",
      "answers": ["babies", "baby", "babe"],
      "correctAnswer": "baby"
  },
  {
      "qid": "p1u2-a11",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "ant, aunt, arent",
      "answers": ["ant", "aunt", "arent"],
      "correctAnswer": "aunt"
  },
  {
      "qid": "p1u2-a12",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "uncle, oncle, under",
      "answers": ["uncle", "oncle", "under"],
      "correctAnswer": "uncle"
  },
  {
      "qid": "p1u2-a13",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "nephew, niece, liece",
      "answers": ["nephew", "niece", "liece"],
      "correctAnswer": "niece"
  },
  {
      "qid": "p1u2-a14",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "naphew, nephew, niece",
      "answers": ["naphew", "nephew", "niece"],
      "correctAnswer": "nephew"
  },
  {
      "qid": "p1u2-a15",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "coussins, cushions, cousins",
      "answers": ["coussins", "cushions", "cousins"],
      "correctAnswer": "cousins"
  },
  {
      "qid": "p1u2-a16",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "siblings, sibbings, sibings",
      "answers": ["siblings", "sibbings", "sibings"],
      "correctAnswer": "siblings"
  },
  {
      "qid": "p1u2-a17",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "triplets, sons, twins",
      "answers": ["triplets", "sons", "twins"],
      "correctAnswer": "twins"
  },
  {
      "qid": "p1u2-a18",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "triplets, son, twins",
      "answers": ["triplets", "son", "twins"],
      "correctAnswer": "son"
  },
  {
      "qid": "p1u2-a19",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "daughter, doctor, daughtor",
      "answers": ["daughter", "doctor", "daughtor"],
      "correctAnswer": "daughter"
  },
  {
      "qid": "p1u2-a20",
      "questionType": "audio",
      "question": "grantchildren, grandchilldren, grandchildren",
      "answers": ["grantchildren", "grandchilldren", "grandchildren"],
      "correctAnswer": "grandchildren"
  },
  {
    "qid": "p2u3-e1",
    "questionType": "text",
    "question": "We come here for talks, ceremonies or shows.",
    "answers": ["library", "hall", "playground"],
    "correctAnswer": "hall"
  },
  {
      "qid": "p2u3-e2",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "I need to do some research on how many countries there are in the world.",
      "answers": ["music room", "art room", "computer room"],
      "correctAnswer": "computer room"
  },
  {
      "qid": "p2u3-e3",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "I think I ate something wrong. I am having a stomachache.",
      "answers": ["toilet", "lift", "classroom"],
      "correctAnswer": "toilet"
  },
  {
      "qid": "p2u3-e4",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "I didn't have breakfast this morning. I am hungry.",
      "answers": ["garden", "tuck shop", "sick room"],
      "correctAnswer": "tuck shop"
  },
  {
      "qid": "p2u3-e5",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "The bell is ringing. We need to have English lesson now.",
      "answers": ["classroom", "music room", "computer room"],
      "correctAnswer": "classroom"
  },
  {
      "qid": "p2u3-e6",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "Mary wants to borrow the book 'The Little Prince'.",
      "answers": ["hall", "library", "playground"],
      "correctAnswer": "library"
  },
  {
      "qid": "p2u3-e7",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "It rained this morning. Be careful when playing badminton.",
      "answers": ["garden", "classroom", "playground"],
      "correctAnswer": "playground"
  },
  {
      "qid": "p2u3-e8",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "Do you know there are beautiful pink roses? Let’s go check it out!",
      "answers": ["garden", "classroom", "playground"],
      "correctAnswer": "garden"
  },
  {
      "qid": "p2u3-e9",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "Nicole broke her legs. She can't walk up stairs.",
      "answers": ["stairs", "toilet", "lift"],
      "correctAnswer": "lift"
  },
  {
      "qid": "p2u3-e10",
      "questionType": "text",
      "question": "Good morning, class. Today we are going to make a Lego robot.",
      "answers": ["art room", "music room", "STEAM room"],
      "correctAnswer": "STEAM room"
  }
  ]
}
